(Penny:)Okay, you know what?
(Penny:)This is ridiculous.
(Penny:)I've been trying to make
(Penny:)a connection with you all day,
(Penny:)and clearly I'm getting nowhere.
(Beverly:)Well, are you
seeking a connection
(Beverly:)or just some form of validation?
(Penny:)What I was seeking was
some sort of friendship.
(Penny:)But at this point, I'll take you
not insulting me to my face.
(Beverly:)My intention was never
to insult you.
You've been doing it all day!
(Penny:)Do you even know
what an insult is?!
(Beverly:)Well, it's not a clinical term.
(Beverly:)But one example would be
your marrying my son,
(Beverly:)and not inviting me
or even telling me
(Beverly:)the wedding was taking place.
(Penny:)Okay, good example.
(Sheldon:)What about Joss Whedon's work
makes you think he'd be okay
(Sheldon:)with rule-breakers
and line-cutters?!
The Avengers are rule-breakers!
(Man:)Being vengeful is in
their job description!
(Sheldon:)They work for SHIELD,
(Sheldon:)which is a sanctioned department
of the U.S. Government!
(Sheldon:)Do you work for a
sanctioned department
(Sheldon:)of the U.S. Government?